http://www.longwoodgardens.org/privacy

Skip to main content
You are hereHome  /  Privacy
Privacy
Online Privacy Policy
Thank you for visiting Longwood's web site. Ensuring the privacy and security of your personal information is very important to us. We will never share, sell, or rent your personal information with anyone in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement, or unless ordered by a court of law. We maintain a variety of physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect your personal information. We have created this online privacy policy to explain our commitment to your privacy and the protection of your information.
Restrictions on Use
This site is owned and operated by Longwood Gardens, Inc. The information on this site is provided to assist you in planning your visit to Longwood Gardens, and it is for this purpose only that the site may be used. While we encourage you to print information which will help plan your visit, no photographs, images or other materials from our site may be copied, downloaded, transmitted, distributed or used in any other way, including for any commercial use. Also, you may not alter or attempt to alter any materials or information on the site, or the site itself.
Your Privacy
Longwood Gardens and its online partners are committed to maintaining the privacy of those who visit our websites.
Longwood Gardens is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. This information will not be sold or rented to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement.
Longwood Gardens collects information from site visitors at several different points on this website.
This notice applies to all information collected by or submitted to our websites or through other purchases. On some pages, you can opt in to receive email communications, register for events, or send communications to your colleagues. The types of personal information collected on these pages varies, and can include:
Name
Name of recipient/s of gift memberships (if applicable)
Names of family members
Address
Email address
Phone number
Credit Card Information (although this data is not stored)
If at any time you would like to obtain the information we have stored or have the information removed, contact us at questions@longwoodgardens.org. If you do submit personal information to us, we will use that information for the purposes for which it was submitted and also for any one or more of the following reasons:
a. If you join our email list, we will have a record of your email address and all other information you choose to provide. We may send you email from time to time about our activities, as well as any specific issues or publications you have subscribed to.  You will have the opportunity to unsubscribe from our mailing list.
b. If you obtain or renew a Longwood Gardens membership, your information will be used to fulfill the financial transaction you have initiated, and your information will be added to our membership database for maintenance and communications to you regarding your membership.
c. If you make an online purchase, your information will be used to fulfill the financial transaction you have initiated, and your information will be added to our database for communications about the Gardens.
d. If you use our tell a friend (optional), the email address(es) you provide will only be used to send your message – these contacts will not be added to our organizational lists or receive any further communications from us unless they separately decide to join our organization.
Be advised that we use third-party vendors to provide services on this site and in our offline business operations. The information that you submit on this site may be provided to those vendors on a confidential basis so that those vendors can provide services (such as maintaining our database, sending email messages, facilitating our online activities and campaigns, or processing credit card transactions) on our behalf.
From time to time, we partner with other carefully selected cultural organizations in the Philadelphia and Delaware Valley area, so that these organizations may advise you of their events. This gives you the fullest knowledge of cultural happenings in our area. If for any reason you would like to be removed from this partnership list, please email or write to us at the address below and we will take your name off of the list immediately.Email:  questions@longwoodgardens.org
Cookies
We use cookies to store visitors preferences, record session information, such as items that consumers add to their shopping cart, record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit, alert visitors to new areas that we think might be of interest to them when they return to our site, record past activity at a site in order to provide better service when visitors return to our site , ensure that visitors are not repeatedly sent the same banner ads, customize Web page content based on visitors' browser type or other information that the visitor sends.
Links to other Web sites
This Web site may contain links to other Web sites for additional products and services. Longwood Gardens is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. We may place advertising on our Web site that originates from third party advertisers and/or advertising agencies. Even though these advertisements are embedded in our Web site cookies may be assigned by the advertisers and not by Longwood Gardens. Longwood Gardens does not control those cookies.
Financial Transactions
In order to process a membership, it is necessary for Longwood Gardens to gather the member' and/or payor’s name, mailing address, phone, and credit card information. This data is used to verify identity and execute the financial transaction.
If you choose to make a purchase online, you will also have to provide a name, mailing address, phone, as well as your credit card billing information. As this information is collected and transferred over the Internet to our secure server, it is encrypted using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology, the industry standard security technology that is designed to protect sensitive information. We display the GoDaddy SSL Seal to assure you that our web site is authentic and that all transactions are secured by SSL encryption. The credit card information that you provide at the time of purchase is used only to process your renewal or purchase and will not be used for any other purposes. The credit card information is not stored in our systems.
Changes to this policy
Longwood Gardens reserves the right, in its sole discretion and without any obligation, to modify or correct any errors or omissions in any portion of this web site. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically.Contact us for questions:
regarding this policy statement,
the practices of this site,
if you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy,
or to review or request changes to your contact information,
Questions? Please contact:
Longwood Gardens, Marketing and Public Relations E-mail: marketing@longwoodgardens.orgMail: P.O. Box 501Kennett Square, PA 19348
(All day)
Greater Philadelphia Gardens:
Explore America's Garden Capital
